Indian Neck Folk Festival collection, 1961-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings, 1961-2014
  - John McCutcheon children's concert, April 16, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR250)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - John McCutcheon concert, April 16, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR251)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. "Only 1 song, 'This Land is Your Land'".
  - Michael Cooney concert, November 5, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR246)
  - Michael Cooney concert, November 5, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR247)
  - Joe and Kathy Hickerson concert, December 3, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR244)
  - Joe and Kathy Hickerson concert, December 3, 1983, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR245)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR080)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR081)
    Cassette 2 of 4
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR082)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR083)
  - George Russell concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR304)
    First set. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - George Russell concert, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR305)
    Second set. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - Broken String Band concert, January 7, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR278)
  - Broken String Band concert, January 7, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR281)
  - Alastair Anderson concert, March 2, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR279)
  - Alastair Anderson concert, March 2, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR280)
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR282)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Friday evening concert featuring Ray Owen, John Pearse, and Mary Faith Rhoads.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR283)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Friday evening concert featuring Ginger and David Hildebrand, Debby McClatchy, and Iron City Morris Men.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR284)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Friday evening concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR285)
    Pennsylvania Folk Festival. Singer-Songwriter workshop with Ray Owen, Dan Duggan, Chris Farrell, Debby McClatchy, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR286)
    Blues workshop with Toni Milto (host) and Moses Rascoe.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR287)
    Fiddle workshop with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Eugene O'Donnell, and Bruce Young. Banjo workshop with Bob Carlin, Debby McClatchy, and John LaRose.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR288)
    Hammered dulcimer workshop with Mary Faith Rhoads and Dan Duggan.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR289)
    Ceilidh with Mick Moloney, Don and Susan Jennings, John LaRose, Bruce Young, Ray Owen, and Eugene O'Donnell.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR290)
    Stories for Children with Dave Krysty and Marcia Bowers.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR291)
    Dulcimer workshop with John Pearse, Mary Faith Rhoads, and Susan Jennings.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR292)
    Childrens' Concert with Dan Duggan, David and Ginger Hildebrand, and Dave Krysty.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR293)
    Tall Tales and Legends with James Y. Glimm.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR294)
    Instrument building workshop. Hammered dulcimer with John Pearse and George Balderose.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR295)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert with George Balderose, Mick Moloney and Eugene O'Donnell, Moses Rascoe, and Dave Krysty.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR296)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert with Dave Krysty, and Feet First Cloggers with the Moonshine Dreamers.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR297)
    Old-Time music workshop with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Bob Carlin, Debby McClatchy, the Moonshine Dreamsers, Dan Duggan, and John LaRose. Topical songs/women's songs workshop with Karl Williams, John Pearse, Mary Faith Rhoads, Ray Owen, and Chris Farrell.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR298)
    Sunday PM fiddle workshop.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR299)
    Old-Time music workshop with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Bob Carlin, Debby McClatchy, the Moonshine Dreamers, Dan Duggan, and John LaRose. From the British Isles to Appalachia workshop with Mick Moloney (host), Eugene O'Donnell, Don and Susan Jennings, Buck Dancer's Choice, Debby McClatchy, and John LaRose.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 25, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR300)
    Guitar workshop with John Pearse (host), Moses Rascoe, Dave Krysty, and Karl Williams.
  - Rev. Dan Smith and Moses Roscoe concert, August 14, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR301)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Series. Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Rev. Dan Smith and Moses Roscoe concert, August 14, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR302)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Indian Neck Folk Festival Concert Series. Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Kinvara concert, September 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR303)
  - John Jackson concert, November 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR306)
  - John Jackson concert, November 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR307)
  - Soldier's Fancy concert, December 15, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR308)
  - Soldier's Fancy concert, December 15, 1984, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR346)
  - John McCutcheon children's concert, January 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR309)
  - John McCutcheon concert, January 19, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR344)
    Evening 1. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - John McCutcheon concert, January 20, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR345)
    Evening 2. Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival.
  - Cliff Haslam concert, February 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR310)
  - Cliff Haslam concert, February 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR311)
  - Broken String Band concert, March 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR347)
    Sponsored by Indian Neck Folk Festival. Harrisburg Area Community College.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 22, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR314)
    Tape 1. Friday evening concert featuring Helen Schneyer and the Jorgovan Orchestra.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 22, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR315)
    Tape 2. Friday evening concert featuring Bo Stauffer and Ojczyzna.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR319)
    Jorgovan Orchestra concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR320)
    Hammered dulcimer workshop with Tom Jolin, Dan Duggan, and Henry Koretzsky.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR321)
    Music of the British Isles with David and Ginger Hildebrand, Donna Campion, Don and Susan Jennings, and Helen Schneyer.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR322)
    Topical Songs and Singer-songwriters with Bo Stauffer, Chris Farrell, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR323)
    Unusual instruments workshop with Mark Gilston, Ojczyzna, Jorgovan Orchestra, and Peter Campion.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR324)
    Dwayne Thorpe mini-concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR325)
    Dan Duggan mini-concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR326)
    Victorian Parlor Songs with Helen Schneyer.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR327)
    Music of the Kalmyks with Dave and Ginger Hildebrand.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR328)
    Fiddle workshop with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Bob Buckingham, Stan Green, Ginger Hildebrand, and John Winship.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR329)
    Don and Susan Jennings mini-concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR330)
    Mark Gilston mini-concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR331)
    Blues workshop with Dwayne Thorpe, Don Jennings, and Karl Williams.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR332)
    Children's concert with Dan Duggan, David and Ginger Hildebrand, and Don and Susan Jennings.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR333)
    Saturday evening concert with Mark Gilston (opens concert with bagpipes), Dwayne Thorpe (traditional American songs, Washington, PA), and the Old World Folk Band (Klezmer, Harrisburg).
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 23, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR334)
    Saturday evening concert with Marion Barnes (storytelling, Philadelphia), and Ensemble Svadba (Yugoslavian music).
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR335)
    Gospel workshop with Helen Schneyer and Dwayne Thorpe.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR336)
    Bo Stauffer mini concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR337)
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR338)
    Old-Time Music workshop with Bob Hartman-Berrier, Bob Buckingham, Dan Duggan, Don and Susan Jennings, Larry Marshall, and Dwayne Thorpe.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR339)
    Marion Barnes (storytelling).
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR340)
    Karl Williams mini concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR341)
    Old World Folk Band mini concert.
  - Pennsylvania Folk Festival, March 24, 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR342)
    Chris Farrell mini concert.
  - Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen concert, April 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR348)
  - Sally Rogers and Howie Bursen concert, April 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR349)
  - Lucy Simpson and Rock Creek, May 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR312)
  - Lucy Simpson and Rock Creek, May 1985, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR350)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1986, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR084)
    Cassette 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Maggi Peirce, Bruce Hutton, Shelly Simpson, Allan Block, Martha Burns, Kathy Hickerson, New Athens String Band, Peppermint Sisters, Drew Smith, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1986, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR085)
    Cassette 2 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1986, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR086)
    Cassette 3 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1986, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR087)
    Cassette 4 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR088)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR089)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1987, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR090)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR091)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording, Saturday evening.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR092)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording, Saturday evening.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1988, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR093)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording, Saturday evening.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR094)
    Cassette 1 of 4. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR095)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR096)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR097)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival sessions, 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR351)
    After dinner sings and Kaufmann.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival sessions, May 1989, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR352)
    Singing session at the Dining Hall, Mother's Day weekend. Nova Scotia Ceilidh recorded from radio station CJFZ, Antigonish, Nova Scotia, during vacation, July 1989.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR098)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Dave Howard, Matty Levine, West Chester Boys, Jan Greene, 4-Gone Conclusions, Kev Sweeney and Tania Wulff, Bob Clayton, Paul Kramer, George Stephens, and Members in Good Standing.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR099)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR100)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring David Jones, Suzy Neane and Nat Hewitt, Pete the Spy, Caroline Paton, and Cliff Haslam.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR353)
    Sunday morning sing, dining hall.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR354)
    Sunday afternoon sing.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1990, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR355)
    Singing and session.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR101)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR102)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR103)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1991, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR104)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR105)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR106)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR107)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR108)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 1992, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR356)
    Fiddle session at the Lodge, and fiddle sessions with some singing.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR109)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR110)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR111)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR112)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 8, 1993, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR357)
    Indian Neck sessions with Bob Walser, Neal MacMillan, Uillean Pipes and Breton Chanter. Dining Hall sessions, synagogue sessions, and miscellaneous.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR113)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR114)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR115)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR116)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1994, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR117)
    Indian Neck Folk Festival recording featuring Pete Kraemer, Judy Cook, Pete the Spy, Barbara Carns, Jan Green, Dick Levine, Herb Nickel, Jerry Epstein, Suzanne Mrozak, Caroline Paton, Linn Schultz, Helen and Riki Schneyer, Lisa Neustadt, Mary LaMarca, Mark Gilston, Lucy Simpson, and Maddy DeLeon. Made for Jonathan Eberhart and Gerry Parsons.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1995, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR118)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording. Sound engineer, Dick Swain. Recording, Tim Brown and Bob Hartman-Berrier.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1995, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR119)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording. Sound engineer, Dick Swain. Recording, Tim Brown and Bob Hartman-Berrier.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1995, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR120)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival recording. Sound engineer, Dick Swain. Recording, Tim Brown and Bob Hartman-Berrier.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1996, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR121)
    Cassette 1 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring the Sandal Shop Players, Kossoy Sisters, Susannah Branch, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Kate Spencer, Shona and Jane Rothfield, Harvey Tolman, Bob McQuillen, Rick Lee and David Howard, Ben Borscht and the Beats, Down East Wests, Dave and the Cowgirls, Peter Hoover and Peggy Haine, Helen Schneyer, and the Lonesome Family Sisters.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1996, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR122)
    Cassette 2 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring Koyuki Smith, Banjo raffle announcement, Jerry Epstein, Joan Sprung, Sara Grey, David Jones, Barbara Carns, Yorkist Ballad Charade, Lisa Neustadt and the Angel Band, Matt and Janine Levine, Dick, David, and Devi Levine, Susan Burke and Bob McQuillen, Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, JoEllen Bossun, Lisa Constable, Susie Whiting, Sandal Shop Players, Allan Carr, Bob Stewart, and Bob McQuillen and Deanna Stiles.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1996, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR123)
    Cassette 3 of 3. Indian Neck Folk Festival concert featuring the Sidekicks vs. Tone-deaf, Dave McFish (Dave Diamond, Bob Clayton, Pete Kraemer, and George Stephens), John and Susan Burke with Susan Sterngold and Lisa Constable.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 1996, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR359)
    Cassette 1 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring the Sandal Shop Players (Allan Block, Mike Rivers, and Ralph Lee Smith), the Kossoy Sisters (Irene Saletan and Ellen Christenson), and Susannah Branch with Kate Spencer, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, and Ken Sweeney), Shona and Jane Rothfield, Harvey Tolman and Bob McQuillen, Rick Lee and Dave Howard, Ben Borscht and the Beats (John and Susan Burke, Drew Smith, Mike Resnick, and Susan Sterngold), Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Down East and Wests (Sue and Charlie West), Sandal Shop Players (Allan and Paul Block), Dave and the Cowgirls (Dave Howard, Linda Schrade, and Kate Spencer), Peter Hoover and Peggy Haine, Helen Schneyer, Lonesome Family Singers (Dave Kiphuth, Linda Schrade, and Bob Stuart), and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 11, 1996, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR360)
    Cassette 2 of 2. Saturday evening concert featuring Koyuki Smith, banjo raffle announcement, Jerry Epstein, Sara Grey, and Joan Sprung, David Jones, Barbara Carns, the Yorkist Ballad Charade, Lisa Neustadt and the Angel Band, Matt Levine and Janine Smith, Dick, David, and Devi Levine, Susan Burke and Bob McQuillen, Ken Sweeney and Tom Hodgson, JoEllen Bosson, Liza Constable, Suzie Whiting, Sandal Shop Players, Allan Carr, Bob Stuart, Deanna Stiles, and others.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1997, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR124)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1997, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR125)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival concert, 1997, 1 sound cassette: analog. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR126)
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 1997, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR361)
    DAT 1 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring Roy Berkeley, Harvey Tolman, Andy May, Kate Spencer and Susannah Branch, Neil Rossi, Tim and Miki Woodbridge, Ken Sweeney, Alice Backer, Wally McNow, Kossoy Sisters (Irene Saletan and Ellen Christenson), Rick Lee, Linda Schrade and Dave Kiphuuth, Allison Kiphuth, Susannah Branch, Shona Rothfield, Helen Schneyer, Lisa Neustadt and the Peppermint Sisters, Ben Borscht and the Beats, and Jan Greene and Liz Downey.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 1997, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR362)
    DAT 2 of 3. Saturday evening concert featuring Anne Schnior, Joanie Bronfman, Neal MacMillan, Lorraine and Bennett Hammond, Riki Schneyer, Wally Macnow, Yorkist Ballad Charade Society, Sara Grey and Joan Sprung, Tom Gibney, Debby McClatchy, Kathy Westra, Dick Levine, David Jones, Lui Collins, Circle of Friends (Dave Kiphuth, Linda Schrade, Bob Stuart), Betty and Norman McDonald, Murray Callahan, Jane Rothfield and Susan Sterngold.
  - Indian Neck Folk Festival, May 10, 1997, 1 sound cassette (DAT): digital. (Item-id AFC 2016/002: SR363)